https://asumh.edu/pages/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
1600 South College St.
Mountain Home, AR 72653 870.508.6100
Contact Entry
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting the web sites of Arkansas State University - Mountain Home (ASUMH). Your privacy is very important to us. We have created this statement to demonstrate our commitment to on-line privacy and to comply with Arkansas Act 1713 of 2003.We collect no personal information about you when you visit our sites, unless you choose to make such information available to us. When you visit any site hosted by ASUMH, our server automatically recognizes the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed our site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or any other personal information.In addition, we monitor the volume and timing of access to the site by collecting information on the date, time, and pages accessed by visitors. The information we collect is used to better understand general site usage patterns, improve site usability, and improve the content of the site. None of this information is shared with other organizations or tied to any individual user.If you choose to share personal information with us -- by sending us an email message or filling out an electronic form with personal information -- we will use the information only for the purposes you authorized. Some of the information may be saved for a designated period to comply with Arkansas' archiving policies, but we will not disclose the information to third parties or other government agencies, unless required to do so by state or federal law.ASUMH sites contain links to other sites, not hosted by ASUMH. Neither ASUMH, nor any ASUMH employee, are responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites.
MY CAMPUS PORTAL
ACADEMIC CALENDAR
ASUMH LIBRARY
COURSE SCHEDULE
ACADEMIC CALENDAR
ADMISSIONS
Important Forms
APPLY
1600 South College St.
1600 South College St.
1600 South College St.
1600 South College St.
